<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Read It</string>

    <string name="str_title_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="str_title_help">Help</string>
    <string name="str_title_make_your_own_read">Make Your Own Read</string>
    <string name="str_title_browse_it">Browse It</string>
    <string name="str_title_audio_settings">Audio Settings</string>
    <string name="str_title_our_other_apps">Our Other App</string>
    <string name="str_title_images">Images</string>
    <string name="str_title_pdf_files">PDF Files</string>
    <string name="str_title_recent_voice">Recent Voice</string>

    <string name="str_start_typing_here">Start typing here…</string>
    <string name="str_send">Send</string>
    <string name="str_camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="str_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="str_skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="str_fb_data">218149285671521</string>
    <string name="str_flurry_app">JVGXYTFK2PVNJ4RJBNVJ</string>
    <string name="str_password">Password</string>
    <string name="str_logo_image">logo image</string>
    <string name="str_voice_selection">Voice Selection</string>
    <string name="str_email_id">Email Id</string>
    <string name="str_confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="str_sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="str_or">or</string>
    <string name="str_login_with_google">Login with Google</string>
    <string name="str_login_with_facebook">Login with Facebook</string>
    <string name="str_already_have_an_account">Already have an account? Login!</string>
    <string name="str_login">Login</string>
    <string name="str_british_accent">British Accent</string>
    <string name="str_american_accent">American Accent</string>
    <string name="str_content_image">content image</string>
    <string name="str_new_here">New here? </string>
    <string name="str_sign_in"> Sign In!</string>
    <string name="str_faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="str_terms_and_privacy_policy">Terms and Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="str_app_info">App Info</string>
    <string name="str_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="str_storage_usage">Storage Usage</string>
    <string name="str_data_usage">Data Usage</string>
    <string name="str_voice_speed">Voice Speed</string>
    <string name="str_tamil">Tamil</string>
    <string name="str_marathi">Marathi</string>
    <string name="str_hindi">Hindi</string>
    <string name="str_accent_selection">Accent selection</string>
    <string name="str_english">English</string>
    <string name="str_language_selection">Language Selection</string>
    <string name="str_female_voice">Female Voice</string>
    <string name="str_male_voice">Male Voice</string>
    <string name="str_audio_settings">Audio Settings</string>
    <string name="str_our_other_apps">Our Other Apps</string>
    <string name="str_help">Help</string>
    <string name="str_lbl_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="str_lbl_no">No</string>
    <string name="str_lbl_exit_from_app">Do you want to close the app?</string>
    <string name="str_enter_url_here">Enter URL here</string>
    <string name="str_bookmarks">Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="str_recent_search">Recent Search</string>
    <string name="str_recent">Recent</string>
    <string name="str_next">Next</string>
    <string name="str_previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="str_recent_audios">Recent Audios</string>
    <string name="str_more_options">More Options</string>
    <string name="str_copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="str_reload">Reload</string>
    <string name="str_lbl_logout_from_app">Do you want to Logout from App ?</string>
    <string name="str_50mins">50 mins</string>
    <string name="str_60">60%</string>
    <string name="str_speak">Speak</string>
    <string name="str_left">left</string>
    <string name="str_right">right</string>
    <string name="str_login_data">Login to get access to read \nmore than millions books</string>
    <string name="str_pdf">pdf</string>
    <string name="str_field_cant_be_empty">Field can\'t be empty</string>
    <string name="str_error_valid_email">Please enter valid Email-Id</string>
    <string name="str_error_minimum_8">Minimum 8 characters</string>
    <string name="str_error_maximum_15">Maximum 15 Character</string>
    <string name="str_error_pswd">Required at least 1 Uppercase letter, 1 Lowercase letter, 1 Number and 1 Special character</string>
    <string name="str_bookmark">Bookmark</string>
    <string name="str_share">Share</string>
    <string name="str_paste">Paste</string>
    <string name="lbl_no_check_internet">No Internet Connection</string>
    <string name="str_share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="str_give_feedback">Your Feedback</string>
    <string name="lbl_username">We want to know what you thought of your experience at \n our App Read It so we\'d love to hear your feedback.</string>
    <string name="lbl_email_id">Email-Id</string>
    <string name="lbl_mobile_no">Mobile No.</string>
    <string name="lbl_submit">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="str_rate_us">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="str_error_valid_mobile">Invalid Mobile No</string>
    <string name="str_terms_n_condition">
ReadIt
        \n
\nPrivacy Policy of ReadIt
\n
\nPrivacy Policy
\nEffective date: July 23, 2018
\n
\nReadIt (\'us\', \'we\', or \'our\') operates the website and the ReadIt mobile application (the \'Service\').
\n
\nThis page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. This Privacy Policy for ReadIt is powered by FreePrivacyPolicy.com.
\n
\nWe use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.
\n
\nInformation Collection And Use
\nWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
\n
\nTypes of Data Collected
\nPersonal Data
\nWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (\'Personal Data\'). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
\n
\nEmail address
\nCookies and Usage Data
\nUsage Data
\nWe may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device (\'Usage Data\').
\n
\nThis Usage Data may include information such as your computer\'s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
\n
\nWhen you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
\n
\nTracking &amp; Cookies Data
\nWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.
\n
\nCookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
\n
\nYou can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
\n
\nExamples of Cookies we use:
\n
\nSession Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
\nPreference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
\nSecurity Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
\nUse of Data
\nReadIt uses the collected data for various purposes:
\n
\nTo provide and maintain the Service
\nTo notify you about changes to our Service
\nTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
\nTo provide customer care and support
\nTo provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
\nTo monitor the usage of the Service
\nTo detect, prevent and address technical issues
\nTransfer Of Data
\nYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
\n
\nIf you are located outside India and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to India and process it there.
\n
\nYour consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
\n
\nReadIt will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
\n
\nDisclosure Of Data
\nLegal Requirements
\nReadIt may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
\n
\nTo comply with a legal obligation
\nTo protect and defend the rights or property of ReadIt
\nTo prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
\nTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
\nTo protect against legal liability
\nSecurity Of Data
\nThe security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
\n
\nService Providers
\nWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (\'Service Providers\'), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
\n
\nThese third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
\n
\nAnalytics
\nWe may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.
\n
\nGoogle Analytics
\n
\nGoogle Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
\n
\nFor more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy &amp; Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
\n
\nLinks To Other Sites
\nOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party\'s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
\n
\nWe have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
\n
\nChildren\'s Privacy
\nOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (\'Children\').
\n
\nWe do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
\n
\nChanges To This Privacy Policy
\nWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
\n
\nWe will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the \'effective date\' at the top of this Privacy Policy.
\n
\nYou are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
\n
\nContact Us
\nIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
\n
\nBy email: readtts@gmail.com
    </string>

    <string name="str_faqs">
       \n FAQ\'s
    \n\n Q: Can I download eBooks on to my hand held device?
\n\n
\nA: In most cases, yes. This does depend on which operating system your hand held device is running however, as different eBook formats are compatible with different operating systems. For detailed information on which eBook formats are compatible with your hand held device, check our device guide.
  \n\n
\nQ: What are the benefits of reading ebooks?
\n
\nA: In most cases, ebooks are cheaper than paper books.
Instantly available worldwide - just download the ebook instead of waiting for "snail mail" or local release.
Full Text Search available - Search our entire database of ebooks for a specific phrase or keyword.
Convenient - imagine loading several novels and a few magazines onto a portable reading device before you go on holiday.
Quick to download - the average novel takes only 3-4 minutes.
You can build a whole library of digital books.
Users can do research and create or organize content.
ebook reading software is free and easy to download from the internet.
  \n\n
\nQ: Can I download books I bought previously onto my iPhone, iPad or iPod Touch using your reader software?
\n
\nA: cYes, you can import or download all previously purchased books onto your apple device using Ebook Reader if the books are available in EPUB or PDF format and are DRM free.
\n
\n
\n Q: Will I be able to view my eBooks offline using the Ebook Reader for iOS and Android?
\n
\nA: Yes. You just need to sync with your bookshelf and download the ebook the first time. Once the ebook is downloaded onto your device, you can read them offline anytime anywhere!




    </string>
    <string name="str_splash">splash</string>
    <string name="str_enjoy_listening_millions_of_free_ebooks_and_many_more">Enjoy listening \n millions of free eBooks \nand many more</string>
    <string name="str_name">Name</string>
    <string name="str_get_pdf">Get PDF</string>
    <string name="str_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="str_select_all">Select All</string>
    <string name="str_fetching_data">Fetching data ...</string>
    <string name="str_favicon">favicon</string>
    <string name="str_read_selected_text">Read Selected Text</string>
    <string name="str_no_pdf_viewed">No Pdf Viewed</string>
    <string name="str_no_image_viewed">No Image Viewed</string>
    <string name="str_rotate">Rotate</string>
    <string name="str_read_specific_selected_text">You can select specific text and listen too...</string>
    <string name="str_home">home</string>


    <!-- App -->
    <string name="app_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="app_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="app_close">Close</string>
    <string name="list_empty">Current list is empty</string>
    <string name="album_title_bookmarks">Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="album_title_history">History</string>
    <string name="album_title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="album_title_files">Files</string>
    <string name="album_title_pass">Login data</string>
    <string name="album_untitled"> </string>
    <string name="notification_content_holderTitle">Opened tabs …</string>
    <string name="notification_content_holder">… Click to View Pages</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search</string>


    <!-- Menu -->
    <string name="main_menu_tabPreview">Open tab preview</string>
    <string name="main_menu_new_tab">New tab (background)</string>
    <string name="main_menu_new_tabOpen">New tab (foreground)</string>
    <string name="main_omnibox_input_hint">Search or type URL</string>
    <string name="menu_open_with">Open link with …</string>

    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_quit">Quit</string>
    <string name="menu_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="menu_delete_list">Delete list</string>
    <string name="menu_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="menu_notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="menu_closeTab">Close tab</string>
    <string name="menu_download">Open downloads</string>

    <string name="menu_share_screenshot">Share screenshot</string>
    <string name="menu_share_link">Share link</string>

    <string name="menu_save_screenshot">Save screenshot</string>
    <string name="menu_save_home">Save at Home</string>
    <string name="menu_save_login">Save login data</string>
    <string name="menu_save_bookmark">Save as bookmark</string>
    <string name="menu_save_as">Save as …</string>
    <string name="menu_save_pdf">Save as PDF</string>
    <string name="menu_share_pdf">Share PDF</string>
    <string name="menu_share_pdfToast">Complete. Open file manager to share?</string>

    <string name="menu_other_searchSite">Search on site</string>
    <string name="menu_other_help">Help</string>


    <!-- AndroidAgo -->


    <!-- Dialog -->
    <string name="dialog_toggle_title">Fast toggle</string>
    <string name="dialog_toggle_hint">To apply immediately, please press the \"OK-button\" below.</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_hint">Title:</string>
    <string name="dialog_extension_hint">Extension (for example: \".jpg\"):</string>
    <string name="dialog_se_hint">https://www.google.com/search?q=</string>
    <string name="dialog_sign_in_username">Username</string>
    <string name="dialog_sign_in_password">Password</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_custom">Custom</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_download">Do you want to download the file?</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="dialog_content_resubmission">Would you like to resubmit your data?</string>
    <string name="dialog_content_ssl_error">The certificate of the site is not trusted. Proceed anyway?</string>


    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="setting_label">Settings</string>

    <!-- Browser setting -->
    <string name="setting_title_browser">Browser Settings</string>
    <string name="setting_title_clear_control">Data Control</string>
    <string name="setting_title_start_control">Start Control</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_clear_control">Clear your browser data or decide what data will be cleared when you leave
    the application.</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_start_control">Decide which components of the browser will be enabled on start.</string>

    <string name="setting_title_search_engine">Search Engine</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_search_engine">Here you can choose your preferred search engine or set a custom one.</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_search_engine_google">Google</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_search_engine_duckduckgo">DuckDuckGo</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_search_engine_startpage">StartPage</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_search_engine_bing">Bing</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_search_engine_baidu">Baidu</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_search_engine_startpage_de">StartPage (de)</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_search_engine_searx">Searx</string>

    <string name="setting_title_inverted">Inverted colors</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_inverted">If checked, content will be rendered in a inverted grey scale mode. This
    is a kind of \"night mode\".</string>

    <string name="setting_title_font">Font size</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_font">Change the font size for displaying websites.</string>

    <string name="setting_title_remote">Remote content</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_remote">Enable remote content, which is not directly from the website you are visiting.
        Disabling this is more secure, faster and saves data volume. But some content will not be displayed anymore.</string>


    <!-- Browser start -->
    <string name="setting_title_images">Images</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_images">Enable Network images. Disabling could be useful to save mobile data and to load
    websites faster.</string>
    <string name="setting_title_cookie">Cookies</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_cookie_delete">If enabled, all cookies will be deleted. Also the Cookies of trusted websites.</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_cookie">Enable Cookies. Cookies are small text files, which are stored on your device. Websites
    use them for example to store user settings (for example search settings). But they could also be used to collect personal
        user data. Third party cookies (they collect user data for advertising) are always disabled.</string>
    <string name="setting_title_whitelistCookie">Cookie whitelist</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_whitelistCookie">If you disable Cookies, you can use this whitelist to allow sites you
        trust to use save cookies.</string>

    <string name="setting_title_javascript">JavaScript</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_javascript">Enable JavaScript. Many websites need JavaScript for their functionality (menus,
        loading and displaying images, …). But they are also a risk and can be used for attacks.</string>
    <string name="setting_title_whitelistJS">JavaScript whitelist</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_whitelistJS">If you disable JavaScript, you can use this whitelist to allow sites you
        trust to use javascript.</string>

    <string name="setting_title_adblock">AdBlock</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_adblock">Enable AdBlock to block annoying ads. Sites also load faster when enabled.</string>
    <string name="setting_title_whitelist">AdBlock whitelist</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_whitelist">Allow these sites to show ads. Some sites do not work, when AdBlock is enabled.</string>

    <string name="setting_title_location">Location</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_location">Allow websites to access your location. Some websites (like Google maps for navigation)
        need this enabled.</string>

    <string name="setting_title_history">History</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_history">Save the history of visited websites.</string>


    <!-- Browser clear -->
    <string name="clear_summary">All files will be exported to the \"Documents\" directory of your sd-card. Each export will overwrite the
        old one. To restore there must be a file with the right name in the directory.</string>
    <string name="clear_menu_done_all">Done all</string>
    <string name="clear_title_quit">Clear when application exits</string>
    <string name="clear_summary_quit">Every time you quit \"Read It Browser\" all above checked data will be deleted.</string>
    <string name="clear_title_bookmarks">Clear Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="clear_title_cache">Clear Cache</string>
    <string name="clear_title_cookie">Clear Cookies</string>
    <string name="clear_title_history">Clear History</string>
    <string name="clear_title_indexedDB">Clear \"indexed databases\" and \"local webview storage\"</string>

    <string name="clear_title_deleteDatabase">Delete database</string>
    <string name="clear_summary_deleteDatabase">Delete the whole database (Startpage, bookmarks, history and all whitelists).</string>


    <!-- App setting -->
    <string name="setting_title_app">App Settings</string>
    <string name="setting_title_ui">Behavior/UI</string>
    <string name="setting_title_data">Backup</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_ui">Change the behavior and ui of the app to suit your preferences.</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_data">Import and export several app data (whitelists, bookmarks).</string>

    <!-- App behavior -->
    <string name="setting_title_hideToolbar">Hide toolbar</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_hide">Use the whole screen when scrolling through websites. If you press the back button you will
    leave fullscreen mode.</string>
    <string name="setting_title_omnibox_control">Omnibox Control</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_omnibox_control">Swipe omnibox left/right to switch tabs</string>
    <string name="setting_title_background">Open links</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_background">Display a notification and open links in background. If disabled links will open
    immediately.</string>
    <string name="setting_title_themeDark">Light theme</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_themeDark">You like it a little bit brighter? Do it!</string>

    <string name="setting_title_nav">Navigation button</string>
    <string name="setting_title_nav_pos">Position</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_nav_pos">Decide where the \"Navigation Button\" will be placed.</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_nav_pos_right">Right</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_nav_pos_left">Left</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_nav_pos_center">Center</string>

    <string name="setting_title_nav_show">Hide</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_nav_show">Hide the \"Navigation Button\" when toolbar is shown.</string>

    <string name="setting_title_tab">Start tab</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_tab">What should be shown at the start of \"Read It Browser\"? The Start Page, you bookmarks, …</string>

    <string name="setting_title_confirm_exit">Confirm browser exit</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_confirm_exit">Confirmation dialog when closing browser.</string>

    <string name="setting_title_confirm_tab_close">Confirm tab close</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_confirm_tab_close">Confirmation dialog when closing a tab.</string>

    <string name="setting_title_toolbar">Toolbar</string>
    <string name="setting_hide_always">Hide always</string>
    <string name="setting_hide_down">Only while scrolling down</string>
    <string name="setting_hide_never">Never hide</string>

    <string name="setting_hideNav_always">Hide always</string>
    <string name="setting_hideNav_toolbar">When toolbar is showing</string>


    <!-- Data -->
    <string name="setting_title_export_bookmarks">Export Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="setting_title_import_bookmarks">Import Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="export_bookmarks">export_bookmarks</string>

    <string name="setting_title_export_whitelist">Export AdBlock whitelist</string>
    <string name="setting_title_import_whitelist">Import AdBlock whitelist</string>
    <string name="export_whitelistAdBlock">export_whitelist_AdBlock</string>

    <string name="setting_title_export_whitelistJS">Export JavaScript whitelist</string>
    <string name="setting_title_import_whitelistJS">Import JavaScript whitelist</string>
    <string name="export_whitelistJS">export_whitelist_Javascript</string>

    <string name="setting_title_export_whitelistCookie">Export Cookie whitelist</string>
    <string name="setting_title_import_whitelistCookie">Import Cookie whitelist</string>
    <string name="export_whitelistCookie">export_whitelist_Cookie</string>

    <string name="setting_title_export_database">Export database</string>
    <string name="setting_title_import_database">Import database</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_export_database">Export the whole database (Startpage + previews, History, Bookmarks) to your
        sd-card. Your login data will not be backed up.</string>
    <string name="title_database">Database</string>
    <string name="hint_database">This will delete all your current settings and data. Will you proceed?</string>


    <!-- Others setting -->
    <string name="setting_title_others">Others</string>
    <string name="setting_title_license">License</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_license">\"Read It Browser\" is completely free (as in freedom) and open source.</string>
    <string name="setting_title_appSettings">App settings</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_appSettings">Open the system app settings for \"Read It Browser\". There you can,
        depending on your Android version grant permissions, clear the app data and so on.</string>
    <string name="setting_title_community">Contributing</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_community">See who contributed something to this project. Or do you want to help with further
        development, report an issue or just get the latest news relating to my projects?</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_changelog">Show the latest changelog to see what\'s new.</string>

    <!-- Toast -->
    <string name="toast_add_bookmark_successful">Bookmark Successfully Added</string>
    <string name="toast_add_to_home_successful">Successfully added to Home</string>
    <string name="toast_add_to_home_failed">Failed to add to Home</string>
    <string name="toast_add_whitelist_successful">Successfully added Domain</string>
    <string name="toast_already_exist_in_home">Already exist in home</string>
    <string name="toast_copy_successful">Successfully copied</string>
    <string name="toast_delete_successful">Successfully deleted</string>
    <string name="toast_domain_already_exists">Domain already exists</string>
    <string name="toast_export_successful">Exported as:&#160;</string>
    <string name="toast_export_failed">Failed to export</string>
    <string name="toast_import_successful">Imported count:&#160;</string>
    <string name="toast_import_failed">Failed to import</string>
    <string name="toast_input_empty">You haven\'t input anything</string>
    <string name="toast_invalid_domain">Invalid domain</string>
    <string name="toast_load_error">Can\'t load this URL</string>
    <string name="toast_load_in_background">Loading in background</string>
    <string name="toast_new_tab_successful">Successfully opened in a new tab</string>
    <string name="toast_open_file_manager_failed">Failed to open File Manager</string>
    <string name="toast_refresh_failed">Can\'t refresh this page</string>
    <string name="toast_relayout_successful">Successfully Relayout</string>
    <string name="toast_share_failed">Can\'t share this page</string>
    <string name="toast_start_download">Starting download</string>
    <string name="toast_wait_a_minute">Please wait for a moment</string>
    <string name="toast_titleConfirm_delete">Do you really want to delete the entry?</string>
    <string name="toast_titleConfirm_paste">Copy data to clipboard?</string>
    <string name="toast_titleConfirm_pasteUN">Username</string>
    <string name="toast_titleConfirm_pastePW">Password</string>
    <string name="toast_error">Uuups. Something went wrong.</string>
    <string name="toast_newTitle">Entry already exists. Please enter new title.</string>
    <string name="toast_edit_successful">Successfully saved</string>
    <string name="toast_webview_forward">Can\'t load next site</string>
    <string name="toast_entry_exists">Entry exists already.</string>
    <string name="toast_clear">Do you really want to clear?</string>
    <string name="toast_permission_title">Permission is needed</string>
    <string name="toast_permission_sdCard">\"Read It Browser\" needs the permission to \"read and write on your storage\". This is needed for
    downloading files, the build in file manager and taking screenshots. If you don\'t grant the permission yet, you can do it
    later in the settings.</string>
    <string name="toast_permission_sdCard_sec">Please grant the permission to \"read and write on your storage\" in the settings.</string>
    <string name="toast_permission_loc">\"Read It Browser\" needs the permission to \"access your location\". This is requested from some
        websites for example when they offer some kind of navigation. If you don\'t grant the permission yet, you can do it
    later in the settings.</string>
    <string name="toast_restart">You must restart \"Read It Browser\" to apply changes. Close now?</string>
    <string name="toast_quit">Do you want to quit \"Read It Browser\"?</string>
    <string name="toast_close_tab">Do you want to close current tab?</string>
    <string name="toast_closeNotification">Close all opened websites.</string>
    <string name="toast_downloadComplete">Download complete. Open file manager?</string>
    <string name="toast_unsecured">This website uses an unsecured connection (\"http\"). Do you want to try a secure
        connection (\"https\")?</string>
    <string name="toast_backup">Backup data? This will overwrite the old backup.</string>


    <!-- Whitelist -->
    <string name="whitelist_menu_clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="whitelist_edit_hint">Domain</string>
    <string name="whitelist_add">Add</string>
    <string name="str_read_whole_page">Read Whole Page</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="tts_settings">Setting</string>
    <string name="tts_prev">Previous</string>
    <string name="play_pause">Play Pause</string>
    <string name="tts_next">Next</string>
    <string name="tts_close">Close</string>
    <string name="tts_rate">Rate</string>
    <string name="tts_pitch">Pitch</string>
    <string name="languages">Languages</string>
    <string name="voices" >Voices</string>
    <string name="engines">Engines</string>
    <string name="hide">Hide</string>
    <string name="lorem">Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry\'s standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book. It has survived not only five centuries, but also the leap into electronic typesetting, remaining essentially unchanged. It was popularised in the 1960s with the release of Letraset sheets containing Lorem Ipsum passages, and more recently with desktop publishing software like Aldus PageMaker including versions of Lorem Ipsum.  Why do we use it? It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content of a page when looking at its layout. The point of using Lorem Ipsum is that it has a more-or-less normal distribution of letters, as opposed to using \'Content here, content here\', making it look like readable English. Many desktop publishing packages and web page editors now use Lorem Ipsum as their default model text, and a search for \'lorem ipsum\' will uncover many web sites still in their infancy. Various versions have evolved over the years, sometimes by accident, sometimes on purpose (injected humour and the like).</string>


</resources>

